Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
You
Hurry, hurry, hurry! Get up!
I accept that the aircraft
but there's no choice
but to do it
The plane can only crash into the sea
There's no other way
I have to accept my fate
has no choice but to do it
Did you memorize this sentence?
Every cell in my body is collapsing now
By the way
Your workout intensity
You ran three thousand meters nonstop
This level of intensity
Even Zhang Xun's dad isn't as extreme as you
Come on, come on
Let's have breakfast first
Su Ruo
Auntie
It's cold
This scarf
I've never used it
You should wear it
It looks nice
I'll buy her some daily necessities today
She's a young girl
It's not right for her to use our shampoo
Also
Buy her a few more changes of clothes
Got it
You don't need to remind me
No need
It's too much trouble for you, Uncle and Auntie
It's no trouble at all
Sit down, sit down
You
Just settle in and stay with us
Don't be so polite with us
This breakfast
is pretty light
Not sure if it suits your taste
Yu Xingchen, why are you spacing out?
Let your classmate eat
If you don't eat enough breakfast
how will you have energy for class?
Don't exaggerate so much
Su Ruo won't dare stay if you act like this
Are you jealous?
It looks so nice
Uncle, Auntie, we're heading out now
Take care
Be safe
I've always had one regret
It's that I never had
a sweetheart daughter
Yeah, it's a pity
It's too late, all your fault for not trying
Is not having a daughter just my problem?
Of course it's your problem
Sour for a boy, spicy for a girl
Back then
You ate vinegar potato strips every day
It's fine, honey
Even though we didn't have a daughter
we can still have
a daughter-in-law
What are you talking about?
She's still so young
The college entrance exam is coming up
Let's talk after the exam
What are you thinking about?
I'm thinking about something important
Right now, in my heart
the only thing that matters is the exam
Don't worry, you'll get into a good university
Where did you go last night?
I waited all night and you didn't come back
We're at the school gate
I hope you stay rational
Otherwise, I'll call the police
Classmate
Sorry about yesterday
Why not take the money if you have it?
Ruo Ruo, come back tonight
Uncle drank too much before
It won't happen again
Seeing this
Maybe you shouldn't go back yet
I stayed at your place for a night
For a moment
I almost forgot all the unhappy things
Earning money early in the morning makes me happy
What are you doing?
This is the medical fee he gave you
I really can't accept it
What if he tells the teacher I extorted him?
He was in the wrong
but I end up being blamed
You take it
He gave it to you
It's reasonable
You really think things through
I'm an adult, after all
In a few months
I'll be an adult too
When something like this happens
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I'm fine
How can you say you're fine?
Tell me
I can handle it
Yu Xingchen
Good thing you were here for this
Otherwise, it would've been terrifying
But
Teacher Jiang said
Although it's understandable
it's unforgivable
You snuck out of school
and skipped a whole afternoon of class
What punishment do you deserve?
I was at least doing the right thing
It's one thing if Teacher Jiang is unreasonable
but he even punishes me
What about Su Ruo?
Where has she been staying these days?
Did she go home?
I don't know
You have to ask her
Su Ruo
Where did you stay last night?
If you have nowhere to go, come to my place
My home is spacious
Don't worry.
I have somewhere to stay.
It's not some shady motel, right?
Is it legit?
Is it safe?
Is there hot water?
Is it clean?
Sorry to trouble you, uncle and aunt.
It's no trouble at all.
We got some hot water ready for you.
You can take a shower.
Sleep well.
My mom said I'm not allowed to eat this.
Only you can have it.
If you don't eat it,
I'll have to feed you myself.
Don't worry about me.
Someone took me in.
They're really nice to me.
Class is over.
Let me take a few more minutes.
I'll finish explaining this problem.
Delayed again, seriously.
What's wrong, what's up?
Isn't the teacher's time valuable too?
The teacher hasn't complained.
But you guys are already complaining.
This problem—
Who can solve it?
You can step out if you want.
Go stretch a bit.
You could go out too.
No one's expecting you to ace the big questions.
Really?
What do you think?
Sit down.
Before we solve the problem,
Let's emphasize something.
Normally, we focus on the big stuff.
But the college entrance exam is different.
Do what you know first.
Save the big questions for last.
Don't force yourself.
Got it?
Understood.
I've done all I can for her.
If I go back now
and tell Tang Song about her uncle,
the truth should come out.
But even if we find out who killed Su Ruo,
even if he's brought to justice,
Su Ruo still won't come back.
This last big question left—
Should I
solve it or not?
What's wrong with you?
The very existence of women
is proof of quantum entanglement.
You can never predict what they're thinking.
Do you remember
the love letter you read to me last time?
You told me
my deskmate asked you to give it to me.
So what happened?
I couldn't accept her feelings,
but to show polite gratitude,
I just asked her
if she wanted help with her homework.
She said no.
I said that's all I can do for you.
She pretended not to get it, asked what's up.
I said I appreciate your feelings for me,
but I can't accept them.
She denied it.
I told her not to be shy about admitting it.
After all, hormonal response at the biological level
is hard to control.
Then she shoved me.
That's it.
Tell me,
my deskmate is just shy, right?
I really don't get girls.
I don't think you're cut out to understand girls.
You're better suited for scientific research.
By the way,
do you remember
what we said about parallel worlds last time?
Good afternoon, teachers and classmates.
I'm your host, Su Ruo.
Today's daily news
will be brought to you by me.
Not long ago, British physicist Stephen Hawking
held a Time Traveler Party at Cambridge University.
Hawking sent out invitations after the party ended.
No doubt,
this was the ultimate test for time travelers.
Unfortunately,
the time travelers ignored Hawking's party.
Not a single person attended.
So, classmates,
do you think time travelers really exist?
If time travel is possible,
the things we did in the past
how much can they change the future?
That depends on what you changed.
For example,
there's a suspect
who kills the victim in the future.
But I stop
the suspect's crime now.
So in the future,
will the suspect
still kill the victim?
Did you stop the suspect by
locking him up,
or taking away his ability to commit the crime?
Seems like neither.
Then that's not absolute causality.
You only stopped him once.
Maybe you just made him angrier.
He might become more obsessed with the victim.
He could seek revenge.
Say you kill the suspect,
lock him up,
or cripple him.
Then he probably won't harm the victim in the future.
Generally speaking,
if the change isn't strong enough,
the altered timeline
will heal like a wound,
tending to return to the original history.
From the timeline correction and convergence view,
years later,
he'll still go after the victim as he was meant to.
I only stopped Su Ruo's uncle once.
But maybe he'll still abuse her after drinking.
Maybe because of this,
he'll hold a grudge against Su Ruo.
But I don't know
if her uncle is directly
connected to Su Ruo's death.
I can't lock him up either.
What will the future become?
Why hasn't Su Ruo come back yet?
Did her uncle go after her again?
Why did you just get back now?
I don't want anyone to know I live at your place.
So I waited until everyone left.
I took a detour to get here.
Ren Nan hasn't left yet.
He might be waiting for me.
I've been working on practice papers.
I even finished previewing the next two days.
Maybe he got tired of waiting and left.
That's good then.
Your uncle didn't come looking for you, right?
Let's head home then.
Sorry to trouble your parents again.
It's no trouble.
They're really hoping you'll come home.
Let's go.
Mm-hmm.
Su Ruo, let me tell you—
Seafood doesn't have sugar.
You can eat as much as you want.
After lobster, there's still crab.
Scallops and oysters are steaming in the pot.
I'm telling you—
Eating these won't make you gain weight.
Su Ruo—
Auntie.
I bought a few clothes.
Not sure if they'll fit.
Come pick some out.
My parents always said they wanted a daughter.
Guess their wish finally came true.
Su Ruo.
Try them on and show Auntie.
Let's go, Su Ruo, come on.
Go ahead.